<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Tracker</string>

    <string name="ble_not_supported">Bluetooth LE not supported.</string>

    <string name="optimizing">Optimizing...</string>

    <string name="day_dream">DayDream</string>
    <string name="blink_marks">Blink Marks</string>
    <string name="numbers">Numbers</string>
    <string name="chart">Chart</string>
    <string name="blinks">Blinks</string>
    <string name="whack_a_mole">Whack-A-Mole</string>
    <string name="accelerometer">Accel</string>
    <string name="grid_size">Grid size</string>
    <string name="graph_height">Graph height</string>
    <string name="min_threshold">Minimum Threshold</string>

    <string-array name="algo">
        <item>Bandpass</item>
        <item>Curve Fit</item>
        <item>Gestures</item>
        <item>Median Diff Diff</item>
        <item>Driftless</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cursor">
        <item>Circle</item>
        <item>Rectangle</item>
        <item>None</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="pages">
        <item>
            Page 1\nElectrooculography (EOG/E.O.G.) is a technique for measuring the
            corneo-retinal standing potential that exists between the front and
            the back of the human eye. The resulting signal is called the electrooculogram.
            Primary applications are in ophthalmological diagnosis and in recording eye movements.
        </item>
        <item>
            Page 2\nTo measure eye movement, pairs of electrodes are typically placed either above
            and below the eye or to the left and right of the eye. If the eye moves from center
            position toward one of the two electrodes, this electrode "sees" the positive side of
            the retina and the opposite electrode "sees" the negative side of the retina.
        </item>
        <item>
            Page 3\nElectrooculography was used by Robert Zemeckis and Jerome Chen,
            the visual effects supervisor in the movie Beowulf, to enhance the performance capture
            by correctly animating the eye movements of the actors. The result was an improvement
            over the technique used for the film The Polar Express. Electrooculography,
            in addition to other neuromuscular signals, is used as a computer input method
            by the Neural Impulse Actuator.
        </item>
        <item>
            Page 4\nEye tracking is the process of measuring either the point of gaze
            (where one is looking) or the motion of an eye relative to the head.
            An eye tracker is a device for measuring eye positions and eye movement.
            Eye tracking is commonly used in a variety of different advertising media.
            Commercials, print ads, online ads and sponsored programs are all conducive
            to analysis with current eye tracking technology.
        </item>
        <item>
            Page 5\nIn real life humans have a small round focal point at the center of our gaze,
            and outside that region, most things are fuzzy and out of focus. This carries over
            into our perception of virtual environments. Thus, even though most VR gear projects
            a roughly 90 degree field of view, our eyes are only focusing (and bringing into focus)
            a small portion of it at any one time. The rest of any crisp, flawlessly rendered image
            is completely wasted on our eyes. Foveated rendering is a process which uses
            the information given by eye tracking in VR games and other apps to only fully
            render the objects within the direct line of sight of the viewer.
        </item>
        <item>Page 6</item>
        <item>Page 7</item>
        <item>Page 8</item>
        <item>Page 9</item>
        <item>Page 10</item>
        <item>Page 11</item>
        <item>Page 12</item>
        <item>Page 13</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
